Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Labor and Radicalism Photograph Collection PHOTOS.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- National Maritime Union, 585366 (Flat-file 7, Drawer 14)
- National Negro Congress, 585365 (Box 6, Folder 320, Flat-file-folder 3, Tray 3)
- Naughton, Norma F. [CWA Local 1150], 585364 (Box 6, Folder 321)
- New Jersey Industrial Council, Sep 10, 1943; 585363 (Box OS005)
- New Leader, 585362 (Box OS003, Folder 7)
- New Leader, 585361 (Box 6, Folder 322)
- New Workers School, 585360 (Box OS003, Folder 8)
- New Workers School, 585359 (Box 7, Folder 323)
- New York City Council/City Hall Reporters Annual Outing, Jun 28, 1971; 585358 (Flat-file-folder 5, Tray 1)
- New York City Lower Eastside, 585357 (Box 7, Folder 323.1)
- New York Typographical Union No.6, 585356 (Box 7, Folder 324)
- Newspaper Guild [there is nothing in this folder but a cross reference to NP1 Negative file- Brown, Heywood.], 585355 (Box 7, Folder 322.1)
- NLRB (cartoons), 585354 (Box 7, Folder 325)
- No Conscription League of New York, 585353 (Box 7, Folder 326)
- Norden, Albert, 585352 (Box 7, Folder 327)
- O'Hare, Frank and Kate Richards, 585351 (Box 7, Folder 328)
- O'Reilly, Leonora, 585350 (Box 7, Folder 329)
- Oates, Joe (I.W.W.), 585349 (Box 7, Folder 330)
- Oneal, James, 585348 (Box 7, Folder 331)
- Owen, Robert, 585347 (Box 7, Folder 332)
- Padmore, George, 585346 (Box 12, Folder 560)
- Panken, Jacob, 585345 (Box 7, Folder 333)
- Paper Box Makers Union, 585344 (Box 7, Folder 334)
- Peekskill Riots and Concert, 585343 (Box OS003, Folder 5)
- Peekskill Riots and Concert, 585342 (Box 7, Folder 335)
- Peng Shu-Tse, 585341 (Box 7, Folder 336)
- Perkins, Frances, 585340 (Box 7, Folder 337)
- Perlman, Selig, 585339 (Box 7, Folder 338)
- Pesota, Rose, 585338 (Box 7, Folder 339)
- Phillips, Wendell, 585337 (Box 7, Folder 340)
- Pickens, William (NAACP), 585336 (Box 7, Folder 341)
- Piecework, 585335 (Box 7, Folder 342)
- Plekhanov, Georgii Valentinovich, 585334 (Box 7, Folder 343)
- Podmaka, Rose, 585333 (Box 7, Folder 344)
- Porter, Edna, 585332 (Box 7, Folder 345)
- Porter, Winfield P., 585331 (Box 7, Folder 346)
- Posters and Broadsides (from the Tamiment/Wagner Collection)-Reference Prints, 585330 (Box 7, Folder 347)
- Potofsky, Jacob, 585329 (Box 7, Folder 348)
- Powderly, Terence Vincent, 585328 (Box 7, Folder 349)
- Prevey, Margaret, 585327 (Box 7, Folder 350)
- Prisons-Kansas State Penitentiary, 585326 (Box 7, Folder 351)
- Progressive Party, 585325 (Flat-file-folder 3, Tray 2)
- Progressive Party, 585324 (Flat-file-folder 2)
- Progressive Party, 585323 (Box OS006, Folder 4)
- Progressive Party, 585322 (Box 12, Folder 561)
- Quill, Michael J., 585321 (Box 7, Folder 352)
- Quill, Molly, 585320 (Box 7, Folder 352.1)
- Quinn, Charles F.(Pa. Fed. of Labor), 585319 (Box 7, Folder 353)
- Rabinowitz (Shalom Aleichem), 585318 (Box 7, Folder 354)
- Rand School - Folder 1: Auditorium, 585317 (Box 7, Folder 355)
- Rand School - Folder 2: Classroom Scenes, 585316 (Box 7, Folder 359)
- Rand School - Folder 3: Class Photos, 585315 (Box 7, Folder 360)
- Rand School - Folder 4: Group Portraits, 585314 (Box 8, Folder 361)
- Rand School - Folder 4: Group Portraits, 585313 (Box OS006, Folder 1)
- Rand School - Folder 5: Bookstore, 585312 (Box 8, Folder 362)
- Rand School - Folder 6: People's House and Misc. Rand School, 585311 (Box 8, Folder 363)
- Rand School - Folder 7: Tamiment Library: Reception for Mayor of W. Berlin, Willy Brandt, 585310 (Box 8, Folder 364)
- Rand School - Folder 8: Tamiment Library: Tamiment Reception, 585309 (Box 8, Folder 365)
- Rand School - Folder 9: Tamiment Library: Tamiment Library Reception, 585308 (Box 8, Folder 366)
- Rand School - Folder 10: Tamiment Library: Miscellaneous, 585307 (Box 8, Folder 356)
- Rand School - Folder 11: Building, 585306 (Box OS006, Folder 4)
- Rand School - Folder 11: Building, 585305 (Box 8, Folder 357)
- Rand School - Folder 12: Unidentified Portraits, 585304 (Box 8, Folder 358)
- Rand School - Folder 13: Oversize, undated; 585303 (Box OS003, Folder 6)
- Rand School - Folder 13: Oversize, 585302 (Box XOS002)
- Randolph, A. Phillip, 585301 (Box 8, Folder 367)
- Randolph, A. Philip: A. Philip Randolph Educational Fund, 585300 (Box 8, Folder 585)
- Rauschenberg, Walter, 585299 (Box 8, Folder 368)
- Reagan, Ronald, 585298 (Box 8, Folder 369)
- Red International of Labor Unions, Executive Bureau, 585297 (Box 8, Folder 370)
- Reed, John, 585296 (Box 8, Folder 371)
- Renaudel, Pierre, 585295 (Box 8, Folder 372)
- Renner, Karl, 585294 (Box 8, Folder 373)
- Retail Clerks International Association, 1967; 585293 (Box XOS001)
- Reuther, Walter P., 585292 (Box 8, Folder 374)
- Reynolds, Stephen Marion, 585291 (Box 8, Folder 374.1)
- Rillieux, Norbert, 585290 (Box 8, Folder 375)
- Rivera, Diego, 585289 (Box OS003, Folder 7)
- Rivera, Diego, 585288 (Box 8, Folder 376)
- Roberts, Lillian, 585287 (Box 8, Folder 377)
- Robeson, Paul - Folder 1: Portraits, 585286 (Box 8, Folder 378)
- Robeson, Paul - Folder 2: Contact Sheets, 585285 (Box 12, Folder 570)
- Robeson, Paul - Folder 3:Othello, Stratford-on-Avon, 585284 (Box 12, Folder 571)
- Robeson, Paul - Folder 4:At the Front, Spainish Civil War, 585283 (Box 12, Folder 572)
- Robeson, Paul - Folder 5: Rallies, Meetings, and Performances, 585282 (Box 12, Folder 573)
- Robeson, Paul - Folder 6: Award Ceremonies, 585281 (Box 12, Folder 574)
- Robeson, Paul - Folder 7: Events Dedicated to, 585280 (Box 12, Folder 575)
- Robeson, Paul - Folder 8: On Trips to Eastern Europe (Soviet Union and East Germany), 585279 (Box 12, Folder 576)
- Robeson, Paul - Folder 9: With Others, 585278 (Box 12, Folder 577)
- Robeson, Paul - Folder 10: Negatives, 585277 (Box 12, Folder 578)
- Rocker, Rudolph and Milly, 585276 (Box 8, Folder 379)
- Rodriguez, William E., 585275 (Box 8, Folder 380)
- Roosevelt, Eleanor [at Local 2, United Storeworkers, District 65], 585274 (Box 8, Folder 381)
- Rose, Ernestine, 585273 (Box 8, Folder 382)
- Rosenberg, Elmer, 585272 (Box 8, Folder 383)
- Rosenberg, Ethel and Julius, 585271 (Box 8, Folder 384)
- Ross, Edward Alsworth, 585270 (Box 8, Folder 385)
- Rubin, Jay, 585269 (Box 8, Folder 386)
- Russell, Bertrand, 585268 (Box 8, Folder 387)
- Rustin, Bayard, 585267 (Box 8, Folder 388)
- Ruthenberg, Charles Emil, 585266 (Box 8, Folder 389)
- Sacco and Vanzetti, 585265 (Box 8, Folder 390)
- Sandburg, Carl, 585264 (Box 8, Folder 391)
- Sanger, Margaret, 585263 (Box 8, Folder 392)
- Sanial, Lucien, 585262 (Box 8, Folder 393)
- Sasaki, Kohzo, 585261 (Box 8, Folder 394)
- Scheidermann, Philipp, 585260 (Box 8, Folder 395)
- Schneiderman, Rose, 585259 (Box 8, Folder 396)
- Scotto, Anthony, 585258 (Box 8, Folder 397)
- Scottsboro, 585257 (Box 8, Folder 398)
- Seger, Gerhart, 585256 (Box 8, Folder 399)
- Seitz (Mayor of Vienna), 585255 (Box 8, Folder 400)
- Senior, Clarence, 585254 (Box 8, Folder 401)
- Shachtman, Max, 585253 (Box 8, Folder 402)
- Shadid, Michael, 585252 (Box 8, Folder 403)
- Shapler, Joseph, 585251 (Box 8, Folder 404)
- Shaw, George Bernard, 585250 (Box 8, Folder 405)
- Shaw, Lemuel, 585249 (Box 8, Folder 406)
- Sheet Metal Workers - Local 28, 585248 (Box 8, Folder 407)
- Shiplocoff, A.I., 585247 (Box 8, Folder 408)
- Simons, A. M., 585246 (Box 8, Folder 409)
- Sinclair, Upton, 585245 (Box 8, Folder 410)
- Singer, Franz, 585244 (Box 8, Folder 411)
- Slovak Workers Society, 585243 (Box 8, Folder 412)
- Sobell, Morton, 585242 (Box 8, Folder 413)
- Social Democratic Federation, 585241 (Box 8, Folder 414)
- Social Democratic League, 585240 (Box 8, Folder 415)
- Social Democratic Party, 585239 (Box 8, Folder 416)
- Social Democratic Party, 585238 (Box OS006, Folder 2)
- Socialist Party, 585237 (Box 9, Folder 417)
- Socialist Party - California, 585236 (Box 9, Folder 418)
- Socialist Party - Michigan, 585235 (Box 9, Folder 419)
- Socialist Party - New York, 585234 (Box 9, Folder 420)
- Socialist Party - New York, 585233 (Flat-file-folder 3, Tray 3, Flat-file-folder 12, Tray 3)
- Socialist Party - Pennsylvania, 585232 (Box 9, Folder 421)
- Socialist Party - US, May 1920, May 1936, undated; 585231 (Flat-file-folder 6, Tray 2)
- Socialist Party - US, 585230 (Box OS006, Folder 2-3)
- Socialist Party - US, 585229 (Box 9, Folder 422)
- Socialist Party - US, 585228 (Flat-file-folder 4, Tray 2)
- Socialist Party - Workers of the World Unite, Undated (Flat-file-folder 1, Tray 1)
- Societe Cooperative Ouvriere de Bruxelles, 585227 (Box 9, Folder 423)
- Solomon, Charles, 585226 (Box 9, Folder 424)
- Sorge, (Mr. and Mrs.), 585225 (Box 9, Folder 425)
- Sotherton, Alice Hyneman (Mrs. Holland), 585224 (Box 9, Folder 426)
- Spanish Civil War, 585223 (Box 9, Folder 427)
- Stalin, Josef, 585222 (Box 9, Folder 428)
- Stanton, Elizabeth Cady, 585221 (Box 9, Folder 429)
- State, County and Municipal Workers of America (SCMWA), 585220 (Box 9, Folder 587)
- Statue of Liberty, 585219 (Box 9, Folder 430)
- Steamfitter, 585218 (Box 9, Folder 431)
- Stedman, Seyomour, 585217 (Box 12, Folder 562)
- Stedman, Seyomour, 585216 (Box OS006, Folder 1)
- Steinmetz, Charles Proteus, 585215 (Box 9, Folder 432)
- Stevens, Uriah S., 585214 (Box 9, Folder 433)
- Stevenson, Adlai, 585213 (Box 9, Folder 434)
- Stokes, J.G. Phelps, 585212 (Box 9, Folder 435)
- Stokes, Rose Pastor, 585211 (Box 9, Folder 436)
- Stone, Lucy, 585210 (Box 9, Folder 437)
- Strikes - Clothing Workers, 585209 (Box 9, Folder 438)
- Strikes - Dressmakers, 585208 (Box 9, Folder 439)
- Strikes - Miners, 585207 (Box 9, Folder 440)
- Strikes - Miners - Ludlow, CO., 585206 (Box 9, Folder 441)
- Strikes - Pennsylvania, 585205 (Box 9, Folder 442)
- Strikes - Public Workers, 585204 (Box 9, Folder 583)
- Strikes - Railroads, 585203 (Box 9, Folder 443)
- Strikes - Shoemakers - Lynn, MA, 585202 (Box 9, Folder 444)
- Strikes - Steel, 585201 (Box 9, Folder 445)
- Strikes - Textile Workers, 585200 (Box 9, Folder 446)
- Strikes - Textile Workers - Lawrence, MA, 585199 (Box 9, Folder 447)
- Strikes - Textile Workers - Passaic, NJ, 585198 (Box 9, Folder 448)
- Strikes - Textile Workers - Paterson, NJ, 585197 (Box 10, Folder 449)
- Strikes - US, 585196 (Box 10, Folder 450)
- Strikes - White Collar Workers (Miscellaneous), 585195 (Box 12, Folder 584)
- Strong, Anna Louise, 585194 (Box 10, Folder 451)
- Student Non-Violent Coordinating Committee, 585193 (Box 10, Folder 452)
- Stulberg, Louis, 585192 (Box 10, Folder 453)
- Stump (Mayor of Reading, PA), 585191 (Box 10, Folder 454)
- Susman, Bill, 585190 (Box 10, Folder 455)
- Sweatshops, 585189 (Box 10, Folder 456)
- Sweeney, John, 585188 (Box 10, Folder 457)
- Sweet Case, 585187 (Box 10, Folder 458)
- Sylvis, William H., 585186 (Box 10, Folder 459)
- Tamiment - Camp Tamiment, 585185 (Box 10, Folder 460)
- Tamiment Institute, 585184 (Box 10, Folder 461)
- Tamiment Institute - Tamiment Book Award:1956, 585183 (Box 10, Folder 462)
- Tamiment Institute - Tamiment Book Award? 1960's, 585182 (Box 10, Folder 463)
- Tamiment Institute - Tamiment College Essay Contest, 585181 (Box 10, Folder 464)
- Tamiment Institute -Tamiment Book Award:1953, 585180 (Box 10, Folder 465)
- Tandler, Julius, 585179 (Box 10, Folder 466)
- Tanner, Jack, 585178 (Box 10, Folder 467)
- Tarkak, 585177 (Box 10, Folder 468)
- Taxi, Rank and File Coalition, Local 3036 - NYC, 585176 (Box 10, Folder 469)
- Tenayuca, Emma, 585175 (Box 10, Folder 470)
- Thirty Hour Week, 585174 (Box 10, Folder 471)
- Thomas, Norman, 585173 (Box 10, Folder 472)
- Thompson, Carl D., 585172 (Box 10, Folder 473)
- Tobenkin, Paul, 585171 (Box 10, Folder 474)
- Trachtenburg, 585170 (Box 10, Folder 475)
- Trade Unions - Coal Miners - United Mine Workers of America, 585169 (Box 10, Folder 476)
- Trade Unions - Communication Workers of America, 585168 (Box 10, Folder 477)
- Trade Unions - Hospital Workers - 1199, National Union of Hospital and Health Care workers, 585167 (Box 10, Folder 478)
- Trade Unions - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 585166 (Box 10, Folder 479)
- Trade Unions - International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 585165 (Box 10, Folder 480)
- Trade Unions - Needle Workers Industrial Union, 1929; 585164 (Box XOS001)
- Trade Unions - Newspaper Guild - Chicago Strike, 1940, 585163 (Box 12, Folder 563)
- Trade Unions - Office Workers - Bookkeepers, Stenographers, Accountants Union, AFL, 585162 (Box 10, Folder 481)
- Trade Unions - Office Workers - United Office and Professional Workers of America - CIO, 585161 (Box 10, Folder 482)
- Trade Unions - State, County, and Municipal Workers of America (SCMWA), 585160 (Box OS006, Folder 1)
- Trade Unions - State, County, and Municipal Workers of America (SCMWA), 585159 (Box 12, Folder 587)
- Trade Unions - Transport Workers Union, 585158 (Box 10, Folder 483)
- Traubel, Horace, 585157 (Box 10, Folder 484)
- Travellick, Richard F., 585156 (Box 10, Folder 485)
- Trenton 6, 585155 (Box 10, Folder 486)
- Tresca, Carlo, 585154 (Box 12, Folder 564)
- Triangle Fire, 585153 (Box 10, Folder 487)
- Triangle Fire (Reproductions), undated; 585152 (Box OS003)
- Trotsky, Leon, 585151 (Box 11, Folder 488)
- Tucker, Benjamin R., 585150 (Box 11, Folder 489)
- Tunnelworkers Local 147, 585149 (Box 11, Folder 490)
- Turati, Philippo, 585148 (Box 11, Folder 491)
- Twining, Luella, 585147 (Box 11, Folder 492)
- UFT-Local 3882 (NYU), 585146 (Box 11, Folder 493)
- Unemployed Movement, 585145 (Box OS003, Folder 9)
- Unemployed Movement, 585144 (Box 11, Folder 494)
- Unidentified Photographs, 585143 (Box 11, Folder 495)
- Unidentified Portraits, 585142 (Box 11, Folder 496)
- Unidentified Portraits, 585141 (Box XOS002, Folder 1)
- Union Label, 585140 (Box 11, Folder 497)
- Union Square, 585139 (Box 11, Folder 498)
- United Auto Workers, 585138 (Box 11, Folder 499)
- United Garment Workers of America, 585137 (Box 11, Folder 500)
- United Hatters, 585136 (Box 11, Folder 501)
- United Labor Party (19th Century), 585135 (Box 11, Folder 502)
- United States Naval Training Station-Great Lakes, Illinois, Jan 19, 1944; 585134 (Box OS005)
- United States Women's Bureau, Jan 20, 1925; 585133 (Flat-file-folder 6, Tray 3)
- United Steel Workers, 585132 (Box 11, Folder 503)
- United Transportation Union, Cleveland, OH, 585131 (Box 11, Folder 504)
- Untermann, Ernest, 585130 (Box 11, Folder 505)
- USSR, 585129 (Box 11, Folder 506)
- Utility Workers, 585128 (Box 11, Folder 507)
- Vail, Charles H., 585127 (Box 11, Folder 508)
- Vaillant, Edouard, 585126 (Box 11, Folder 509)
- Van Arsdale, Harry (Jr.), 585125 (Box 11, Folder 510)
- Van Kleeck, Mary, 585124 (Box 11, Folder 586)
- Vanderveer, George, 585123 (Box 11, Folder 511)
- Vandervelde, Emile, 585122 (Box 11, Folder 512)
- Vladeck, B. Charney, 585121 (Box 11, Folder 513)
- Vladeck, B. Charney, 585120 (Box OS006, Folder 1)
- Vorse, Mary Heaton, 585119 (Box 11, Folder 514)
- Wagner Family, 1977-1978; 585118 (Box 11, Folder data_value_missing_c4d80cbe763375d6bef24bcf9df9ea3a)
- Wagner, Robert F. (Senator), 585117 (Box 11, Folder 515)
- Wagner, Robert F. (Senator), 585116 (Box OS003, Folder 8)
- Wagner, Robert F. (Senator), 585115 (Flat-file-folder 2)
- Wagner, Robert F. Jr., 585114 (Box 11, Folder 516)
- Wagner, Robert F. III (1944-1993), 585113 (Box 12, Folder 565)
- Waldheim Cemetery, Chicago, IL, 585112 (Box 11, Folder 517)
- Waldman, Louis, 585111 (Box 11, Folder 518)
- Wallace, Henry, 585110 (Box 11, Folder 519)
- Wanhope, Joshua, 585109 (Box 11, Folder 520)
- War, 585108 (Box 11, Folder 521)
- Ward, Lester F., 585107 (Box 11, Folder 522)
- Warren, Fred D., 585106 (Box 11, Folder 523)
- Washington (State) - Centralia, 585105 (Box 11, Folder 524)
- Washington (State) - Montesano Chahalis County, 585104 (Box 11, Folder 525)
- Wattes, Florence, 585103 (Box 11, Folder 526)
- Webb, Sidney, 585102 (Box 11, Folder 527)
- Weizman, Chaim, 585101 (Box 11, Folder 528)
- Western Federation of Miners, 585100 (Box 11, Folder 529)
- Whitman, Walt, 585099 (Box 11, Folder 530)
- Wilson, Lilith Martin, 585098 (Box 11, Folder 531)
- Wise, Stephen S., 585097 (Box 11, Folder 532)
- Women - Employment, 585096 (Box 11, Folder 533)
- Women - Trade Unions, 585095 (Box 11, Folder 534)
- Women and Labor, 585094 (Box 11, Folder 535)
- Women's International League for Peace and Freedom (WILPF), Jan 2, 1925, undated; 585093 (Box 12, Folder 588)
- Women's International League for Peace and Freedom (WILPF), 585092 (Flat-file-folder 9, Tray 4)
- Women's Peace Party WWII, 585091 (Box 11, Folder 536)
- Women's Trade Union League, 585090 (Flat-file-folder 3, Tray 1)
- Women's Union Label League, Local 197, San Diego, CA, 585089 (Box 11, Folder 537)
- Wood, G.W. (Chico, Montana), 585088 (Box 11, Folder 538)
- Workers - Glaziers, 585087 (Box 12, Folder 566)
- Workers - Lace Weavers, 585086 (Box 12, Folder 539)
- Workers - Lumber Industry, 585085 (Box 12, Folder 567)
- Workers - Miners, 585084 (Box 12, Folder 540)
- Workers - Print Shops, 585083 (Box 12, Folder 568)
- Workers - Sign Painters, 585082 (Box 12, Folder 541)
- Workers - Textile, 585081 (Box 12, Folder 542)
- Worksites, 585080 (Box 12, Folder 543)
- World War II, 585079 (Box 12, Folder 544)
- World War II - Civilians, 585078 (Box 12, Folder 545)
- Wright, Clyde, 585077 (Box 12, Folder 545.1)
- Yellow Dog Contract, 585076 (Box 12, Folder 546)
- Young, Arthur H.- Caricaturist/ cartoonist, 585075 (Box 12, Folder 547)
- YPSL (Young People's Socialist League), 585074 (Box 12, Folder 548)
- Yurick, Sol, 585073 (Box 12, Folder 569)
- Zaritsky, Max - Folder 1, 585072 (Box 12, Folder 549)
- Zaritsky, Max - Folder 2, 585071 (Box 12, Folder 550)
- Zetkin, Clara, 585070 (Box 12, Folder 551)
- Unprocessed Material, Undated; 585069 (Box OS006, Folder 1-4)
- Unprocessed photographs, contact sheets, slides, 1942-2010 (Box 13, Box 14)
- Glass Negatives, 1903, undated (Box 15, Box 16)
- Glass Lantern Slides of Puerto Rico, 1902-1926 (Box 17, Box 18)
- Workmen's Circle group portrait, 10th Convention, 1910 (Box Shared Tamiment 032)